Come & Get It
来拿吧
歌手：Selena Gomez
压制:随Feng
When you're ready come and get it
当你准备好了就来吧
Na na na Na na na Na na na
When you're ready come and get it
当你准备好了就来吧
Na na na Na na na Na na na
When you're re-e-e-dy
当你准备好了
When you're ready come and get it
当你准备好了就来吧
Na na na Na na na Na na na
You ain’t gotta worry it’s an open invitation
你不必担心这是一个公开的邀请
I’ll be sittin’ right here real patient
我会坐在这里耐心等待
All day all night I’ll be waitin’ standby
每一天晚上我都会在一旁守着
Can’t stop because I love it, hate the way I love you
放不下只因我喜欢,恨我爱你的方法
All day all night maybe I’m addicted for life, no lie.
整日整夜,也许我会一生都痴迷于此,但我从不撒谎
I’m not too shy to show I love you
我没那么害羞,我敢表达我喜欢你
I got no regrets
我不后悔
I love you much to, much to hide you, this love ain’t finished yet
我很爱你,想把你隐藏起来,不让别人偷走
This love ain’t finished yet…
这还不够,不够
So baby whenever you’re ready…
所以宝贝你准备好的时候…
When you're ready come and get it
当你准备好了就来吧
Na na na Na na na Na na na
When you're ready come and get it
当你准备好了就来吧
Na na na Na na na Na na na
When you're re-e-e-dy
当你准备好
When you're ready come and get it
当你准备好了就来吧
Na na na Na na na Na na na
You got the kind of love that I want, let me get that.
你拥有我想要的那种爱,快给我
And baby once I get it I’m yours no take backs.
宝贝,我得到后我就是你的,无悔
I’m gon’ love you for life I ain’t leaving your side
我会爱你一辈子,我不会离开你
Even if you knock it ain’t no way to stop it
即使你,也没有办法阻止它
Forever you’re mine baby I’m addicted no lie, no lie
你永远是我的,宝贝我上瘾了,我从不撒谎,从不
I’m not too shy to show I love you, I got no regrets.
我没那么害羞,我敢表达我爱你,我不后悔
So baby whenever you’re ready…..
所以宝贝,当你准备好了…
When you're ready come and get it
当你准备好了就来吧
Na na na Na na na Na na na
When you're ready come and get it
当你准备好了就来吧
Na na na Na na na Na na na
When you're re-e-e-dy
当你准备好
When you're ready come and get it
当你准备好了就来吧
Na na na Na na na Na na na
This love will be the death of me
这爱会是我的死亡之期
but I know I’ll die happily
但我知道我会幸福地死去
I’ll know I’ll know I’ll know
我懂我懂我懂
Because you love me so
因为你也爱我
…Yeah!
…Yeah
When you're ready come and get it
当你准备好了就来吧
Na na na Na na na Na na na
When you're ready come and get it
当你准备好了就来吧
Na na na Na na na Na na na
When you're re-e-e-dy
当你准备好
When you're ready come and get it
当你准备好了就来吧
Na na na Na na na Na na na
压制:随Feng